$Wet and Cold	Wet and Cold
$Wet and Cold Status:	Wet and Cold Status:
$Player	Player
$NPCs	NPCs
$Followers	Followers
$Wet	Wet
$Cold	Cold
$Drips	Drips
$Soggy Feet	Soggy Feet
$Rain Blind	Rain Blind
$Rain Gear	Rain Gear
$Rain Gear Options	Rain Gear Options
$Add to Leveled Lists	Add to Leveled Lists
$No Leveled Lists	No Leveled Lists
$Hoods	Hoods
$Cloaks	Cloaks
$Gloves	Gloves
$Backpacks	Backpacks
$Children	Children
$Waterskins	Waterskins
$Breaths	Breaths
$Snowy	Snowy
$Blizzard Blind	Blizzard Blind
$Cold Gear	Cold Gear
$Cold Gear Options	Cold Gear Options
$Survival Gear	Survival Gear
$Survival Gear Options	Survival Gear Options
$Strong Winds	Strong Winds
$Go Home	Go Home
$Full	Full
$Mode:	Mode:
$Default	Default
$Summer	Summer
$Winter	Winter
$1st/3rd Person	1st/3rd Person
$3rd Person	3rd Person
$Enabled	Enabled
$Disabled	Disabled
$All Races	All Races
$No Argonians	No Argonians
$No Nords 6AM-8PM	No Nords 6AM-8PM
$Followers Only	Followers Only
$All Civilians	All Civilians
$Workers Ignore Rain	Workers Ignore Rain
$Blur	Blur
$WCPurchase	Items specific to and distributed by Wet and Cold will be added to leveled lists. There is a chance you will be able to encounter them at general goods merchants and inside house containers.\nAfter enabling this feature and exiting the menus, leveled lists will be permanently modified. This cannot be undone.
$WCPurchaseAsh	Goggles and/or face covers will be added to leveled lists. There is a chance you will be able to encounter them at general goods merchants in Solstheim.\nAfter enabling this feature and exiting the menus, leveled lists will be permanently modified. This cannot be undone.
$WCDrip	Wet drip effects play during rain and after swimming.
$WCFootWet	A light splash sound effect and splash particles play from each footstep when it's raining and after swimming. Does not work on creatures.
$WCBreath	Cold breath effects play in cold regions.
$WCRainBlind	Raindrops will blind you periodically while looking up.
$WCGoHome	NPCs will return home when it rains and will also return home during a blizzard.
$WCRainGear	NPCs will equip hoods and cloaks if their equipment slot is free once it starts raining. If 'No Argonians' is selected, Argonians will not equip rain gear.
$WCColdGear	NPCs will equip fur hoods, gloves and fur cloaks if their equipment slots are free in cold regions. If 'Winter Is Coming' is installed, those fur cloaks may also be equipped by NPCs. If 'Ashes' is installed, NPCs may also equip face covers. If 'No Nords 6am-8pm' is selected, Nords are less likely to equip cold gear items during the day.
$WCMode	Summer: All cold-related features will be disabled. Use this option for summer overhauls.\nWinter: All of Skyrim will be considered cold. Use this option for winter overhauls.
$WCBlizzBlind	NPCs will have more difficulty detecting targets during a blizzard.
$WCWind	Movement speed will be reduced by 15% if caught in a blizzard. Affects NPCs as well.
$WCBlizzBlindPlayer	Snow will blind you periodically during a blizzard. Keep your face down to avoid.
$WCRainGearFollower	Followers will produce and equip rain gear if their equipment slots are free once it starts raining. Argonians will still refuse to equip them unless 'All Races' is enabled.
$WCColdGearFollower	Followers will produce and equip cold gear if their equipment slots are free in cold regions. Nords will still refuse to equip gear during the day unless 'All Races' is enabled.
$WCSurvival	Travelling NPCs may equip backpacks if their slot is free. If 'iNeed' is installed, they may also be equipped with waterskins.
$WCSnowy	Snow accumulation effects will play on the body during snowfall and after swimming in the cold. Dead bodies will become snowy in the cold.
$Installed	Installed
$Ashes/Survival	Ashes/Survival
$Watery Eyes	Watery Eyes
$Ash Gear	Ash Gear
$Ash/Survival Gear Options	Ash/Survival Gear Options
$Face Covers	Face Covers
$Goggles	Goggles
$Dusty	Dusty
$WCWateryEyes	Ash will make your eyes water during ash storms in Solstheim. Keep your face down to avoid or equip goggles.
$WCAshGearNPC	NPCs will produce and equip face covers and sometimes goggles if their slots are free during ash storms in Solstheim.
$WCAshGearFollower	Followers will produce and sometimes equip face covers and goggles if their equipment slots are free during ash storms in Solstheim.
$WCDust	Dust accumulation effects will play over the entire body during ash storms in Solstheim. Swimming or getting wet from the rain will remove the effect. Getting wet from rain to remove the effect relies on either Wet and Cold's 'Drip' effect or 'Rain Blind' enabled.